Arne Oldberg Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-78, 81-85)
  - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and blue and red pencil; 55 p. (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35, Autograph string parts (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35, Autograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35, Autograph brass parts (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35, Autograph percussion parts (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35, Copyist's string parts (Box-folder 40/7)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Photocopy of holograph piano I part (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Photocopy of holograph piano II part (Box-folder 41/2)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Photocopy of holograph full score; 91 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Photocopy of holograph full score; 91 p. [two of two] (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Transparencies of holograph full score; 91 p. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Transparencies of holograph piano parts (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 41/7)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Transparencies of holograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 41/8)
  - Symphonic variations, two pianos and orchestra, op. 40, Transparencies of holograph horn and percussion parts (Box-folder 41/9)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Holograph piano sketch score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and red pencil; 59 p. (Box-folder 42/1)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Holograph full score; p. 1-169, p. 174-266 (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Holograph full score; p. 1-55, "Finale" p. 1-35, sketch, p. 13 (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's first violin parts (Box-folder 43/1)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's second violin parts (Box-folder 43/2)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's viola parts (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's cello parts (Box-folder 43/4)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's bass parts (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's flute parts (Box-folder 43/6)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's oboe and English horn parts (Box-folder 43/7)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's clarinet parts (Box-folder 43/8)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's bassoon parts (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's horn parts (Box-folder 43/10)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's trumpet parts (Box-folder 43/11)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's trombone and tuba parts (Box-folder 43/12)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version, Copyist's harp and percussion parts (Box-folder 43/13)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Holograph two piano score in black ink, with annotations in pencil; p. 1-23, p. 1-17, and p. 1-14 (Box-folder 44/1)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopy of holograph full score; 137 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 44/2)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopy of holograph full score; 137 p. [two of two] (Box-folder 44/3)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Transparencies of holograph full score; 137 p. and 4 p. sketches (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 45/2)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 45/3)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Transparencies of holograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 45/4)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Transparencies of holograph brass and percussion parts (Box-folder 45/5)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph violin I parts (Box-folder 46/1)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph violin II parts (Box-folder 46/2)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph viola parts (Box-folder 46/3)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph cello parts (Box-folder 46/4)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph bass parts (Box-folder 46/5)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph flute parts (Box-folder 46/6)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph oboe and English horn parts (Box-folder 46/7)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph clarinet parts and holograph bass clarinet part (Box-folder 46/8)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph bassoon parts (Box-folder 46/9)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph horn parts (Box-folder 46/10)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph trumpet, trombone, and tuba parts and holograph trumpet I and II parts (Box-folder 46/11)
  - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version, Photocopies of holograph harp and percussion parts (Box-folder 46/12)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Autograph full score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and blue and red pencil; 188 p. (Box-folder 47/1)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Holograph piano score in black ink, with annotations in pencil; 48 p. (Box-folder 47/2)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in pencil; 301 p. (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in blue pencil; 193 p. (Box-folder 48/1)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Photocopy of holograph full score; 211 p. (Box-folder 48/2)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 1-101 (Movements I and II) (Box-folder 49/1)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 102-211 (Movements III and IV) (Box-folder 49/2)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 49/3)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Photocopies of holograph violin I parts and copyist's violin I parts, with photocopies of holograph movement II and holograph pasteovers (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's violin II parts with photocopies of holograph movement II and holograph pasteovers (Box-folder 49/5)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's viola parts with photocopies of holograph movement II and holograph pasteovers (Box-folder 49/6)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's cello parts with photocopies of holograph movement II and holograph pasteovers (Box-folder 49/7)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's bass parts with photocopies of holograph movement II and holograph pasteovers (Box-folder 50/1)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's flute parts with holograph annotations and pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/2)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's oboe and English horn parts with holograph pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/3)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's clarinet parts with holograph pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/4)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's bassoon parts with holograph pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/5)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's horn parts with holograph pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/6)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's trumpet parts with holograph annotations and pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/7)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's trombone and tuba parts with holograph annotations and pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/8)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Copyist's percussion parts with holograph annotations and pasteovers and holograph movement II (Box-folder 50/9)
  - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor, Bells, triangle, harp, and celesta parts, holograph annotations and pasteovers (Box-folder 50/10)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. I. Moderato e sostenuto--allegro, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and blue and red pencil; 77 p. (Box-folder 51/1)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. II. Canzone. Moderato espressivo, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and blue and red pencil; 38 p. (Box-folder 51/2)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Introduzione e scherzo, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and blue and red pencil; 87 p. (Box-folder 51/3)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Photocopy of holograph full score; 169 p. (Box-folder 81/1)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. II. Canzone, Photocopy of holograph full score; 30 p. (Box-folder 81/2)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. II. Canzone, Photocopy of holograph full score; 30 p. (Box-folder 81/3)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. II. Canzone, Transparencies of holograph full score; 169 p. (Box-folder 81/4)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's violin parts, photocopies, and one original violin II part (Box-folder 51/4)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's viola, cello, and bass parts, photocopies, and originals (Box-folder 51/5)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's flute, oboe, and English horn parts (Box-folder 51/6)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's clarinet and bassoon parts (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's horn and trumpet parts (Box-folder 52/2)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's trombone and tuba parts (Box-folder 52/3)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor, Copyist's percussion parts (Box-folder 52/4)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Autograph piano and string parts (Box-folder 52/5)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Holograph flute, violin I parts (Box-folder 52/6)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Autograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 52/7)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Autograph brass, percussion, and harp parts (Box-folder 52/8)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Photocopies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 52/9)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Photocopies of copyist's violin parts (Box-folder 52/10)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone, Photocopies of copyist's viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Sostenuto, Holograph flute III, oboe I, bass clarinet, horn III and IV, and percussion parts (Box-folder 53/2)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. Canzone and III. Finale, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 53/3)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Finale, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 53/4)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Sostenuto, Photocopies of holograph viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 53/5)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Sostenuto, Copyist's string parts, some with annotations by Oldberg (Box-folder 53/6)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Finale, op. 41, Copyist's viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 53/7)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Finale, op. 41, Autograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 53/8)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Finale, op. 41, Autograph brass parts (Box-folder 53/9)
  - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor. III. Finale, op. 41, Autograph percussion and harp parts (Box-folder 53/10)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil and red and blue pencil; p. 3-130; Includes program from Chicago Symphony Orchestra concert, December 31, 1942 and January 1, 1943, taped into front cover. (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score; p. 3-130 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 3-130 (Box-folder 82/3)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopies of copyist's violin parts (Box-folder 54/1)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopies of copyist's viola parts (Box-folder 54/2)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopies of copyist's cello parts (Box-folder 54/3)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopies of copyist's bass parts (Box-folder 54/4)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Copyist's flute parts [movement I] with photocopies of holograph movements II-IV (Box-folder 54/5)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Autograph oboe parts with holograph inserts (Box-folder 54/6)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Autograph clarinet parts with holograph inserts (Box-folder 54/7)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Photocopies of copyist's bassoon parts with holograph inserts (Box-folder 54/8)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Autograph horn parts (Box-folder 54/9)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Autograph trumpet, trombone, and tuba parts (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor, Autograph timpani, piano, and harp parts, with holograph inserts and photocopies of holograph (Box-folder 55/2)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Transparencies of holograph piano score; I. Ballade p. 2-16, II. 8 p., Finale p. 25-36, and extra p. 2 and 16 (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopy of holograph piano score; p. 2-36 (2 copies) (Box-folder 83/1)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopy of holograph full score; p. 2-131 (one of three) (Box-folder 83/2)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopy of holograph full score; p. 2-131 (two of three) (Box-folder 83/3)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopy of holograph full score; p. 2-131 (three of three) (Box-folder 83/4)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 2-131 and 2 draft p. (Box-folder 83/5)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor. II. Nocturne, op. 54, no. 2, Holograph piano score, pasteovers and annotations in pencil; p. 2-10 (Box-folder 55/5)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor. II. Nocturne, op. 54, no. 2, Photocopy of holograph piano score; 8 p. (Box-folder 55/6)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor. II. Nocturne, op. 54, no. 2, Holograph violin solo part (Box-folder 55/7)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 55/8)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopies of holograph viola parts (Box-folder 55/9)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Photocopies of holograph cello and bass parts (Box-folder 55/10)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Flute, oboe, and English horn parts, in copyist's hand (Box-folder 55/11)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Clarinet and bassoon parts, in copyist's hand (Box-folder 56/1)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Holograph clarinet I part (Box-folder 56/2)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Horn and trumpet parts, in copyist's hand (Box-folder 56/3)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Trombone and tuba parts, in copyist's hand (Box-folder 56/4)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Holograph triangle/bells and bass drum/cymbals parts (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor, Harp part, in copyist's hand (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Holograph full score; 52 p. (Box-folder 85/6)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; 56 p. (Box-folder 85/7)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Holograph piano score in black ink, with annotations in pencil; 34 p. (Box-folder 56/7)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Holograph string parts (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Holograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Symphony, no. 7, C minor, Holograph brass, percussion, and harp parts (Box-folder 56/11)
  - Symphony in D major, Festival, Autograph full score; 131 p. (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Theme and variations, op. 49 see Six variations for orchestra, op. 49
  - Trio, E minor, piano, violin, cello, Holograph full score; 78 p. (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Trio, violin, viola, and cello, Holograph parts (Box-folder 57/3)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Photocopy of holograph full score; 47 p. (Box-folder 58/1)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Holograph full score in pencil and pen; I. "c'etait" 21 p., II. "Sa Chanson" 12 p., III. "Insomnie" 20 p. (Box-folder 58/2)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Transparencies of holograph piano-vocal score; 20 p. (Box-folder 58/3)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Photocopy of holograph piano-vocal score; 20 p. (Box-folder 58/4)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Transparencies of holograph full score; 47 p. (Box-folder 58/5)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Holograph woodwind, horn, percussion, and harp parts (Box-folder 58/6)
  - Trois chansons françaises, op. 53, Unfinished transparencies of holograph violin and viola parts (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Trois morceaux for piano, op. 13, Chicago: Clayton F. Summy Co., 1902. (Box-folder 58/8)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in red and blue pencil; 115 p. (Box-folder 59/1)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Photocopy of holograph full score; 114 p. (Box-folder 59/2)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Holograph piano score in black ink, with annotations in pencil and red and blue pencil; 26 p. (Box-folder 59/3)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Photocopy of holograph piano score; 22 p. (book one of two) (Box-folder 59/4)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Photocopy of holograph piano score; 22 p. (book two of two) (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Transparencies of holograph piano score; 22 p. (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Transparencies of holograph full score; 114 p. (Box-folder 59/7)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Transparencies of holograph flute, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, and horn parts (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Copyist's violin parts (Box-folder 60/2)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Copyist's viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Flute parts, one set photocopies of holograph, one set copyist's manuscript (Box-folder 60/4)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Oboe and English horn parts, one set photocopies of holograph, one set copyist's manuscript (Box-folder 60/5)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Clarinet parts, one set photocopies of holograph, one set copyist's manuscript (Box-folder 60/6)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Bassoon parts, one set photocopies of holograph, one set copyist's manuscript (Box-folder 60/7)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Photocopies of holograph horn parts (Box-folder 61/1)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Copyist's horn parts (Box-folder 61/2)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Copyist's trumpet, trombone, and tuba parts (Box-folder 61/3)
  - Twelve variations for orchestra, op. 19, Copyist's percussion and organ parts (Box-folder 61/4)
  - Valsette for two pianos, Photocopy of holograph two piano score; 11 p. (Box-folder 58/9)
  - Miscellaneous Songs
    - Aveu, Transparencies of holograph piano-vocal score; p. 2-5, and additional p. 5 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Keramos, Holograph piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 58/10)
  - Extra Parts
    - At Night, Fantasy for orchestra, op. 38; Concerto for piano and orchestra, no. 1, op. 17, G minor (Box 63)
    - Concerto for piano and orchestra, no. 1, op. 17, G minor (continued), and Concerto for piano and orchestra, no. 2, op. 43 (Box 64)
    - Concerto for piano and orchestra, no. 2, op. 43 (continued); Concerto for piano and orchestra, no. 3, op. 52; Festival overture, op. 29 (Box 65)
    - Festival overture, op. 29 (continued); June Rhapsody, op. 36, and Le son du cor for horn and orchestra (Box 66)
    - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra (continued) and Paolo and Francesca, dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21 (Box 67)
    - Paolo and Francesca, dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21 and The Sea, Fantasy for orchestra, op. 47 (Box 68)
    - Sinfonia, op. 48 and Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major (Box 69)
    - St. Francis of Assisi and Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, E minor version (Box 70)
    - Symphony, no. 1, op. 23, F minor version (Box 71)
    - Symphony, no. 2, op. 34, C minor (Box 72)
    - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor (Box 73)
    - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor (continued) (Box 74)
    - Symphony, no. 3, op. 41, F minor (continued) and Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor (Box 75)
    - Symphony, no. 4, op. 50, B minor (continued) and Symphony, no. 5, op. 54, E minor (Box 76)
    - Symphonic variations, organ and orchestra, op. 35; Theme and variations (Six variations for orchestra, op. 49), and Twelve variations for orchestra (Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous Sketches
    - Andante movement for horn (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Harmony sketches (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Miscellaneous sketches by Arne Oldberg (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Miscellaneous sketchbooks, Northwestern University. Sonate op. 3; 49 p., Composition classes; 8 p., and 1 p., Chopin's The minute waltz (Box-folder 78/1)
    - Miscellaneous sketchbooks, Northwestern University, 62 p. and 12 p. (Box-folder 78/2)
  - Class Notebooks
    - München, 1898-1899, Zweite Klasse, Doppelte Kontrapunckt in Fugenlehre (one of two), 96 p. (Box-folder 62/1)
    - München, 1898-1899, Dritte Klasse, Kanon in Formlehre (two of two), 85 p. (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Loose sheets inserted in München, 1898-1899, Zweite Klasse notebook (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Academie der Tonkunst, München, Music notebooks (one of two), II, 42 p., III, 46 p. (Box-folder 78/3)
    - Academie der Tonkunst, München, Music notebooks (two of two). Notebook beginning: "III to Durchführung," 36 p.; Notebook beginning: "Engführung," 40 p.; Notebook III beginning: "1573, Alte Passions Lied," 40 p.; Notebook III beginning: "Forsetzung der Kanan der Unterquarte," 36 p. (Box-folder 78/4)
  - Arrangements by Oldberg
    - Bach, J.S. Fantasie et Fuga in C minor für Klavier übertragen von Arne Oldberg, op. 12. Chicago: Clayton F. Summy Co., 1907 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus. Fantasia and Sonata [K. 475], arranged for horn by Oldberg, Transparency of horn part in Oldberg's hand (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus. Sonata [K. 283], arranged for horn by Oldberg, Transparency of horn part in Oldberg's hand (Box-folder 58/13)
  - Other Composers
    - Kuhlau, F. Trois Sonates faciles & brillantes pour le pianoforte á quatre mains, op. 66. Hambourg: Chez A. Cranz., 15 p. (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Oscar Oldberg, Miscellaneous sketches (one of two) (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Oscar Oldberg, Miscellaneous sketches (two of two) (Box-folder 62/9)
- Correspondence, circa 1892-1962, undated (Box 86-90)
  Personal, family and professional correspondence.